(Leonard:)Gentlemen.
- Where have you been?
- Nurse's office.
- Asthma attack?
- Asthma, heart. Some kind of attack.
(Leonard:)I'm fine, though.
(Howard:)You guys going to
Professor Tupperman's memorial?
- Probably not.
- Barely knew him.
Yeah, you wouldn't wanna look like you guys
are brownnosing the tenure committee...
(Howard:)...who will all be there.
(Leonard:)- Oh, yeah.
- Meerkats.
(Sheldon:)I won't be able to make our date night
this Thursday, so bad news for you.
(Amy:)You better have a good excuse this time.
(Amy:)Because trimming Q-tips to fit your ears
right is obvious nonsense.
(Sheldon:)First of all, when you say things like that,
people think you're crazy.
Second, the reason I'm canceling...